I wish we have about half an hour
before some friends have to
leave us. We will cry. You
deceived me again. Okay, 945. We have
13 minutes left to finish Nagar. I
can do it without rhinestones and I will do it. We have
finished three and a half chapters. Don't
forget, I owe you two and a half
chapters. Don't worry, I don't forget.
But we did everything right. We went through
them slowly. You have what I need. I'll show you the
first minute of the video. You can turn on
the project. Chapter 1 that we studied
was Pariksha, what, and Ingraya, the
eyes and the object. There is a cool video
that I often enjoy, which has
Heisenberg's uncertainty principle. This
means that there is a problem in quantum
physics. And you are fed up with how we
see things. There is a problem with how light
from the sun hits the earth. There are
problems with this and Stephen Hawking couldn't
figure it out, but we figured it out and now the
problems are ready.
I won't show it in its entirety.
Nagarjuna is strange.
[music]
Okay, it's on the basket. It doesn't make sense.
He says it's all the same in quantum physics. I still
don't know.  How does sunlight
reach the earth? We would die. By
sunlight, we would have no food. We would have no carbon deposits.
This comes from the sun. We don't know how
this happens. It comes from the sun. This is
chapter 3. In
chapter 3, how does it come from the sun?
Say it loudly. Seven hides for 0
dollars. The topic is about what comes from
my Mara. It opens up and creates me and the
sunlight that reaches the earth. And
since sunlight hits the earth,
this seed opens up in your mind, just as
grains grow from the sun. This also happens.
We looked at this in
chapter 3. We finished this chapter at universities. Chapter 4.
What was it about? Research.
Tell me in Sanskrit.
Research. What is Parikshit? What are rickshaws?
What am I? Skanda
X.
Research. 5 parts of a person. And for
this, we can. What's strange about the
elements and the result of their elements. What's
strange about a time traveler? This is what aspirin is.
Aspirin, having Google, is
chemically or a place inside. And when we
get a headache, I remember how my
mother taught me. Take spirin. I used to have a
very
big, good, main thing. My mother said, just
take it.
I remember once, when I was a child, nothing good happened.  It didn't happen I
remember where I was I remember that I was on
my brother's bed and couldn't even get
to my room I'm lying in bed the words
brothers give aspirin
nothing happens I ask mom
mom it didn't work for me anyway the main
bullet it burns take the second one I take 2 I
take in ten minutes anyway the same thing the
main thing will be but again it's up to you
mom I have another spirin dinner I remember
she takes a bottle and says yes for
children you can only take those pills
she says sorry
no more I thunder but I still have a
headache she says very bad
things sometimes we you just have to have a
headache and I'm like this and we are always
faithful to my mom okay mom she says
sometimes
aspirin to work and sometimes aspirin doesn't
work
okay dear side she deceived me
back she was a bad plumber she didn't
tell me truly will give she didn't
understand on the curtain chapter 4 she believes
believed in
how 2 types of atoms are formed in a molecule
inside aspirin she believed in it that there are
two types of atoms in a molecule
she you trusted that aspirin  There are special
atoms,
special molecules, she believed in this, this is the
second example, this is chapter 4, we want a
real example, gear, we wanted a
real example, what was chapter 3 about, about
sunlight, how it reaches the earth,
what was chapter 4 about, aggravation,
chapter 5, yes, percentage and the definition of
space and lokshina, that is, fire is
hot, scorching, these qualities, no one
took this hot, scorching and did not put it on
fire, this is varnish, this sign of this thing
is permissible when things are this chapter and
fire is
hotter than fire does not happen, the game and
itself, what is the practical application of this
I remember that I gave from the teaching in
New York
right before my traffic, three flu
and it was very difficult, taught 18 of these
courses and then it was very difficult
because I made an announcement:
I am leaving New York, we are leaving
and yet, and I remember how I got up saying
I am leaving New York, I need to leave, I am
doing a three-year retreat as a result of the
desert and and there is another teaching at the
shopping center, I gave this teaching at the
shopping center, I say  no metal in their
creation has lokshin he ga she is hard
metal hard it can hold such a
big borrow what holds this shopping
center is metal
and inside it has lokshin
proudly hard and strong true to me this is
hard strong and I remember how I gave this
lecture the last one was in New York before the
retreat it is not metal not steel it is not lokshin it is not hard it is not not
hard and not strong back but not
inside steel this is strong to me
and not hard is in the capital
what holds this roof is that walls it is
your karma it is your seeds your
seeds
hold this roof it is not bricks
forget about it don't think like that
if you want to have a roof over your
head as we say English
if you want to have an apartment a place to
live you must do a
tango line with 13 steps on other people you
must give them a place to live if you
don't do this this building will fall what
happened the World Trade Center hit I
remember that I left like a summer retreat and
suddenly a lot of military planes
you are here  Bubbles in the desert, we're doing a retreat,
suddenly, a lot of planes
are practicing, we're still
here, and we're wondering what's going on. We're here, and we're wondering what's going on.
We don't know. When we left the
retreat, the news came, big
news, a
big newspaper, Kenshin, three pages in
this newspaper,
they came to us, about the interior, these people say, you're the
only people in the world who don't
know yet. Let's talk about what's going on there. What happened to the
International Trade Center?
We're talking about, you know, the last ones,
then you'll go north. IV ball, 30 seconds,
stands.
When she comes into the kitchen, my
husband starts yelling. My husband starts
yelling. I imagine what's going on. I gave a
donut on the table.
What happens when you feel
stressed at home? Sometimes you eat too
much, so we get fat. We also have
too much stress. Even Geshe Michael,
when he was there yesterday evening, I would have gone home. I
ate three porridges before bed. I'm
tired. I eat, and my wife also thinks about it. My husband is
not kind to me. I need to eat something
to feel happy. And yo, a donut will make
me happy.
Listen to pride. I like it, and
this donut will make me happy. It
burns. Which part of this donut is it? Well,  so that's the one that
touches my tongue
and what does it touch the tongue well yes it
touches the tongue of course no no it doesn't
touch that the tip is a donut and touches
what part of the tip touches the tongue that's
impossible that's chapter 6
sugar sugar crystal sugar granule
never touches the tongue because
if they touched they would have to
get inside each other like that they can't
touch like that even if they touch
then a little bit of sugar should become a little bit of the
tongue you see when sugar should
become part of the tongue that's impossible well what
if sugar doesn't become part of the
tongue but then they can't
affect each other they can't you see
if sugar can give flavor to the tongue
without mixing with it then
poop also gives flavor to the tongue because
they don't mix either you see this is a
special white house
storage pu pu everything inside will give
you a good taste why those what why are you
saying this because sugar gives you a
good taste no but sugar in my mouth no it's not
yours marta it can't touch not
only somersaults but if it touches they
cover each other if they touch they
don't mix you see so that
sugar gives you a good taste to your wife in the kitchen
because she's nervous  From what
could be, if sugar gave the bush there
should have been a slight mixing.
If there is no mixing, then the poop in the
toilet also gives a
good taste at the same time because they also do not
mix and pu-pu also does not mix
with the tongue and sugar does not mix with the tongue,
therefore, everything that does not mix with the tongue
should give taste, you see, and if they
mix, then the tongue becomes sugar. This is
impossible. The same as with the professor
in cartoons,
he is like this. I don’t know what’s going on. It is impossible for
Gina to feel
better
from eating this. This is impossible. This is
impossible. The last
question is to understand why the wife
feels more comfortable
after her husband spilled and left. If
she eats a tampon, why Kesha Michaels,
I ate 3 sweet
plates of porridge yesterday. Why does she want to eat? She
wants to feel relaxed and
wants to feel comfortable. Her husband is
angry. I need to eat and a tampon. I don’t
need something sweet. There is too much
stress, so she eats correctly. Does
a tampon give a sweet taste? Does a
donut give comfort? What gives comfort? Trin
tunngle n  From 13 steps, 13-step
tunngle.net, Karama Luther comes to you
through this, at the donut later, you
won't need her tampon, you will be
slim and will feel good
about your husband, this is how we use
these four chapters, how we use them,
this is not just theory, use them
well, use the tangle and use
them in these 13 steps from online
Nagarjuna and Kangle, they
got married this morning, it is understood
that